hulaparkb.com 2019-03-05

# Privacy Policy

hulaparkb Inc. (here and after hulaparkb.com) recognizes that privacy is very important to our customers and we have taken steps in accordance with accepted industry practice to protect the security and privacy of any personal information customers provide to us. This includes Customers' names, addresses, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses and any information that can be linked to an individual. 

As part of our commitment to our customers, hulaparkb.com has implemented the following comprehensive privacy policy. 

**Customers have control of their personal information.**

hulaparkb.com will not release personal information about customers without their permission, except as required by court order, subpoena or applicable law, or as set forth below. 

By using our website, customers agree to allow hulaparkb.com to contact them about promotions and materials of interest. Customers who do not wish to be contacted may notify us at any time either in writing, by telephone or in person at one of our stores. 

To opt-out of receiving email communication from hulaparkb, you may click the one-click unsubscribe link at the bottom of all emails or email us at tailynn@hulaparkb.com and asked to be removed from our mailing list. 

**hulaparkb.com does not collect personally identifiable information through passive methods that are hidden from the Customer, except as described below.**

When you visit our websites, you will be assigned a permanent 'cookie' (a small, unique identifier text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is to identify you when you visit our site so we can enhance and customize your online experience. 

We also collect certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during a visit to our websites. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, browser type and the address of a referring Website, if any. We collect this information to enhance the quality of your experience during your visit to our site and will not sell or rent this information to any third parties. 

**We will enforce strict security measures to prevent unauthorized access to or use of customers' personal information.**

hulaparkb.com treats personal and individual information as confidential and restricts the number of employees who have access to it. We also follow strict procedures on its use. Employees who violate the Company's customer privacy safeguards are subject to disciplinary action up to and including termination. 

**We welcome your comments and questions.**

Customers may access their own readily available and easily retrievable purchasing information upon written request. 

As changes occur in hulaparkb.com's business, technology and the laws that affect this policy, we will continue to review and revise this policy. The use of information we gather now is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time of use. We may send you periodic notices of changes to our policy, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our website periodically to see the current policy. 

If you have any questions or concerns, please contact one of our customer representatives e-mail through the Customer Service section of our website at tailynn@hulaparkb.com .
